Contact

rntoday@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rntoday (LinkedIn)

www.facebook.com/ melissayanezowens/ (Personal) rntoday.wordpress.com/ (Blog) RNToday.INFO (Company)

Top Skills

Spanish

Public Speaking

Public Relations

Languages

Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Supoort
INTL NURSES ASSOCIATION
NIH STROKE SCALE CERTIFIED
Basic Life Support

Publications

I CHOSE TO FOLLOW GOD, AGAINST PARENTAL ALIENATION

MelissaBeth Yanez-Owens

Native American Nurse Activist

Houston, Texas

Summary

Registered Nurse working to promote the safety of our children by preventing physical, emotional, mental and sexual abuse around the world. Bringing awareness to Parental Alienation Syndrome. Counseling in identifying and preventing the behavioral traits between an emerged psychologically programmed child and alienating parent. We are here to help you and your children in preventing ESTRANGEMENT. Preventing child abuse.

Learn how to win against Parental Alienation and against the corrupt judicial system.

We specialize in truth and prevention of abuse of your child's mind. Nonprofit organization Against Parental Alienation preventing the rewiring of your child's mind into being a corrupt government follower of evil.

Our goal is to provide accurate resources and information to preserve wellness and health in our children by preventing abuse within the corrupt us government of kidnapping ,selling and abusing our children.

Experience

RNTODAY -A NONPROFIT FOR CHILDREN'S RIGHTS

Founder

April 2013 - Present (7 years 4 months)

United States

We are a nonprofit organization REGISTERED WITH THE STATE OF TEXAS AND set up to help those affected by Parental Alienation. RN investigating allegations of abuse involving high profiled custody cases. Assist parents in ruling out false allegations and save children from the abusive effects of family law. Consulting parents in depth about the negative psychological effects PAS has on the child . Consulting, teaching training parents on recognizing signs and symptoms of PAS. Preventing abuse and preventing ESTRANGEMENT between parents and children.

RnToday ,Parental Alienation
American Nurse Activist
November 2013 - Present (6 years 9 months)
Worldwide

EQUAL PARENTING RIGHTS ACTIVIST .

THE FATHERS MOVEMENT CIVIL RIGHTS ACTIVIST

Kindred Healthcare Registered Nurse October 2019 - December 2019 (3 months) Houston, Texas Area

IMU -bedside nurse with detailed assessment of patient's physical and emotional needs in providing the best care for the critically ill, ventilator dependent patients requiring long term treatment with the healing process. Worked diligently with the excellent respiratory staff for effective weaning process required for the patient to be discharged.

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions PRN Nurse July 2019 - September 2019 (3 months) Houston, Texas Area

Per diem nurse . Bedside nurse for different units including , Med Surg Telemetry, IMCU, ER Hold , Observation Unit.

Assessment , Nursing Diagnosis, Planning, Intervention, Treatment and Evaluation.

Working diligently in collaboration with full time staff in promoting the optimal health and progressive outcome for patient.

The Hospitals of Providence
Travel Registered Nurse
March 2019 - April 2019 (2 months)
El Paso, Texas Area

bedside nurse ,Assessment and treatment of the Cardiac patient- including status post cardiac cath patient, stent placements for prevention of MI . Status post Pacemakers placements. Collaborated with Surgeon and Cardiologist in best care for the patient.

Telemetry monitoring. Effective monitoring of lab values and cardiac enzymes while up close monitoring of patient's heart rhythm. Continuous physical assessment of patient throughout treatment and updating progress to MD and working with other disciplines in effective treatment for patient.

United Staffing Solutions, Inc. (USSI)
Travel Nurse
March 2019 - April 2019 (2 months)
United States

USSI is very helpful in assisting nurses with the travel assignment that best suits the nurse and the facility. They seem to be fair and support the travel nurse while still filling in the much needed staffing assignment for the hospital. They also assisted with the best suited hotel accommodation near the facility, easy fast access to work while having the home away from home accommodation.

Allegheny Health Network
Trauma General Surgery
August 2018 - November 2018 (4 months)
Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania

Trauma Surgery Oncology, bedside nurse. ADPIE of patient status post surgical intervention. Status post critically wounded including but not limited to status post MVA, STROKE, CA, GUN shot wound patients. Monitoring of drain outputs, labs, heart rhythms, continuous assessment and evaluating patient's overall healing process and interventions collaborated with physicians in assisting patient with the best outcome for discharge.

OakBend Medical Center Registered Nurse June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months) Rosenberg, Texas

bedside nurse, Med Surg, Surgical floor staff nurse. Assessment, Planning, Interventions, continuous evaluation and monitoring of patient's progress, status post surgical interventions, collaborating with MD for effective healing of patient for discharge.

Nightingale Nurses Travel RN August 2017 - December 2017 (5 months) Florida

Grateful for this company to have assisted me with providing me employment in taking a job as bedside nurse in which I was able to apply my best skills and customer service in assisting these patient's with their physical and emotional healing.

Texas Health Resources RN PCU TELE

August 2017 - October 2017 (3 months)

United States

bedside nurse ,Progressive Care Unit status post CABG , Telemetry monitoring patient's heart rhythm receiving non titrated drips.

Status post care of the Cardiac patient after cardiac cath lab, stent placements, pacemaker.

Kindred Healthcare Registered Nurse February 2017 - June 2017 (5 months)

Houston, Texas Area

bedside nurse, med surg telemetry floor

Houston Northwest Medical Center, Inc. Registered Nurse March 2015 - May 2015 (3 months) United States

bedside nurse, Med Surg Telemetry floor

St. Joseph's Medical Center RN Agency postpartum and med surg tele April 2012 - February 2013 (11 months) United States

bedside nurse, post partum, med Surg telemetry

Tomball Regional Medical Ctr Medical Surgical Nurse June 2012 - October 2012 (5 months) United States

bedside nurse, med surg floor

Education

Brighton College - Company
Paralegal Nursing, Law (2019 - 2020)

Lone Star College System

Associate of Arts and Sciences (AAS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2006 - 2011)

Coastal Carolina University

Bachelor's degree, Political Science and Government · (2014)